const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'אָב',
    answers: ['vader', 'voorvader'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אָח',
    answers: ['broer', 'broeder'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אָחוֹת',
    answers: ['zus', 'zuster'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אִישׁ',
    answers: ['man'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אִשָׁהׁ',
    answers: ['vrouw'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אֵם',
    answers: ['moeder'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אַָדָם',
    answers: ['mens', 'mensheid'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אֱלֹהִים',
    answers: ['God'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'בֵּן',
    answers: ['zoon'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'בַּת',
    answers: ['dochter'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'יִשְׂרָאֵל',
    answers: ['Israël', 'Israel'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'לֵב',
    answers: ['hart'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'עִיר',
    answers: ['stad'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'עוֹף',
    answers: ['vogel', 'vogels'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'עַם',
    answers: ['mensen', 'volk'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'קוֹל',
    answers: ['stem'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'רֹאשׁ',
    answers: ['hoofd'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שֵׁם',
    answers: ['naam'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson2Vocabulary: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson2-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 2 – Woordenschat',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson2Vocabulary
